# Naseem Khan



## Contact ADDRESS

Rawalpindi, PAKISTAN

## <u>Email:</u>

naseemkhan@gmail.com

#### Languages

HTML CSS C++

## Summary

Senior Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTMLS, CSS, C++. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

## Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

### Experience

Graphic Designing. Website Developer Fiverr(2018-2020), PPH(2018-2019)

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
  Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

## Education

FSC PreEngineering From Step College, DOING BACHELOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE FROM PMAS(2021-2024)

#### Certifications

ADOBE CERTIFICATIONS IN PHOTOSHOP AND ILLUSTARTOR